And we can also sign in, so we're able to sign in, but we can not as well, right?
But for a better experience, I prefer signing in, right?
So I click on this login option and it also has a dark mode, so let me turn it on, it's better for me.
I click on login/signup and now continue with Google.
And I will be redirected to the page that I can choose among my Google accounts, as you see.
So it says choose an account to continue to quill bot.
So I choose my preferred Gmail account to continue with quill bot.
And again, it says Google will allow quill bot to access these info, so I click continue.
I have no problems.
And at the end, as you see, we will be signed in to a quill bot account using our Google account.